Alert Icon

Upcoming Event:

Wednesday, June 26, 2024 | 9:00 AM – 10:00 AM – [Finance and Audit Committee Meeting](https://www.lipower.org/board-of-trustees/board-meetings/2024-06-26/06-26-24-finance-and-audit-committee-meeting/) – LIPA, 333 Earle Ovington Blvd. 4th Floor, Uniondale, NY 11553

    ### About Us
    
    As a not-for-profit utility, we’re here to serve our local community.​

    ### Board of Trustees
    
    Get information about upcoming Board and Committee Meetings, as well as full biographies of all members of the LIPA Board.

    ### Finance
    
    Understand LIPA's financial role and view materials related to investor relations and the Utility Debt Securitization Authority.

    ### Operational Partners
    
    View contracts with our service provider, along with performance reports and annual utility metrics.​

    ### Information Resources
    
    LIPA provides a variety of resources that help you find everything from reports and contracts, to statewide policies and environmental assessments.

    ### Procurement
    
    Explore current procurement opportunities with LIPA and PSEG Long Island along with major contracts and reports.

    ### Contact Us
    
    Want to get in touch with LIPA? You can email, call, or use our chat service to contact our staff.​

Search: 

Search

**Privacy** Policy
==================

Last modified: March 11, 2024

**Introduction**  
Thank you for visiting the Long Island Power Authority’s (“LIPA’s”) website. LIPA (“Company” or “We”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website located at: https://www.lipower.org (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

* On this Website.
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

* Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party; or
* Any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or through the Website.  
    Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time see ‘Changes to Our Privacy Policy’ (below). Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Children Under the Age of 16**  
Our Website is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at 516-222-7700.

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**  
We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

* By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, email address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline\] (“**personal information**”);
* That is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
* About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, and usage details, including the following:
    * The Internet Protocol (IP) address and domain name of your internet service provider. The IP address is a numerical identifier assigned either to your internet service provider or directly to your computer, which can be used to direct internet traffic to you;
    * The type of browser and operating system you used;
    * The date and time you visited this site;
    * The webpages or services you accessed at this site and the files that you downloaded; and
    * The URL or address of the website you visited prior to coming to this website and from which any webpage on this site was linked.

We collect this information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us.
* Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons,\] \[and other tracking technologies\].
* \[From third parties, for example, our business partners.\]  
    Information You Provide to Us  
    The information we collect on or through our Website may include:
* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. We may also ask you for information if you report a problem with our Website or send us a question.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
* Details of transactions you carry out through our Website.
* Your search queries on the Website.
* The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic information formats that you send to us.
* The information contained in your e-mail or communication will be used to access customer services, respond to you, address the issues you identify, further improve this website, or forward your e-mail or communication to another agency or entity for appropriate action.
* Information received by us from your communication with this Website, including your e-mail address, is not collected for commercial marketing purposes, and we do not sell or distribute such information for commercial marketing purposes.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “**posted**”) on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties (collectively, “**User Contributions**”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

_**Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies**_  
As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). Click the CookieYes widget for information on how you can opt out of behavioral tracking on this website and how we respond to web browser signals and other mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice about behavioral tracking.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
* Speed up your searches.
* Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies)**. A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for cookies, see ‘Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information’ (below).
* **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Website and our emails\] may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

**Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**  
Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see ‘Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information’ (below).

**How We Use Your Information**  
We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

* To present our Website and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights.
* To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**Disclosure of Your Information**  
We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.  
We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of LIPA’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by LIPA about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
* With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
* To enforce or apply our terms of use [Terms of Use](https://www.lipower.org/terms-of-use/) and other agreements.
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of LIPA, our customers, or others.

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**  
We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

* Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) on the NAI’s website at: https://thenai.org/

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**  
You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and sending us an email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.lipower.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

If you delete your User Contributions from the Website, copies of your User Contributions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages, or might have been copied or stored by other Website users. Proper access and use of information provided on the Website, including User Contributions, is governed by our [terms of use](https://www.lipower.org/terms-of-use/).

**Your State Privacy Rights**  
State consumer privacy laws may provide their residents with additional rights regarding our use of their personal information. This Website is intended for New York State residents only.

**Data Security**  
We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. We urge you to be careful about giving out information in public areas of the Website like message boards. The information you share in public areas may be viewed by any user of the Website.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**  
It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Information**  
To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:  
LIPA, 333 Earle Ovington Blvd. 4th Floor, Uniondale, NY 11553 or call 516.222.7700

4867-3432-0809, v. 1

Footer Menu

### About LIPA

### Board Meetings

### Careers

### Contact Us

© 2024 LIPA

Utility Menu

Return to Top

Type to Search: 

Quick Links
